export const FlashCardQuestions = [
	{
		question: "How many Stage Names did Dwayne Johnson perform under? List them",
		answer: "3: Flex Kavana, Rocky Maivia, The Rock",
	},
	{
		question: "What year did 'The Rock' make his WWF debut?",
		answer: "1996 as Rocky Maivia",
	},
	{
		question: "When did Rocky Maivia become 'The Rock'?",
		answer: "1997 Rocky turned 'heel' and began refering to himself in the third person",
	},
	{
		question: "What was the first championship belt won by DJ, and who did he defeat to win it?",
		answer: "Feb 13, 1997 he won the InterContinental Championship from Hunter Hearst Helmsly aka 'Triple-H",
	},
	{
		question: "Name 'The Rock's 2 main signature moves",
		answer: "The RockBottom and The People's Elbow",
	},
	{
		question: "What records does 'The Rock' solely hold in regards to WWF broadcasts?",
		answer: "Most Raw shows main-evented in one year, most SmackDown shows main-evented in one year",
	},
	{
		question: "What show gets its name directly from 'The Rock's rhetoric?",
		answer: "SmackDown, from his 'lay the smackdown' phrase",
	},
	{
		question: "Who did 'The Rock' defeat to win his first WWF Championship?",
		answer: "Mankind",
	},
	{
		question: "What was the name of the group of heals headed by Vince McMahon that 'The Rock' was a part of early on?",
		answer: "The Corporation",
	},
	{
		question: "Which event main-evented by 'The Rock' was the most bought pay-per-view worldwide in WWE history?",
		answer: "WrestleMania XXVIII",
	},
];